<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home</title>
    <link>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/</link>
    <description>Recent content on home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 23:04:47 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.spargonaut.wtf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Get Gud Wit Git</title>
      <link>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/posts/lets-get-good-with-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 23:04:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/posts/lets-get-good-with-git/</guid>
      <description>Lets Get good with git!
Over the course of my career, I&amp;rsquo;ve used a variety of programming languages, IDEs and other tools to write software.
One tool that has almost always been there, is Git.
These are some of my favorite resources for learning, brushing up, or simply playing with git.
 learngitbranching.js.org  The tutorials are great, and they come with a CLI to practice your git commands This site is probably my favorite in this list because it builds a diagram of your commit stack as you run the commands in the tutorials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with kotlin</title>
      <link>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/posts/getting-started-with-kotlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 16:05:22 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/posts/getting-started-with-kotlin/</guid>
      <description>When I started with Kotlin in the spring of 2018, it had already been on my radar for a while. My reluctance to hang out on the bleeding edge and various other reasons kept me from diving into it before that.
Once I got started though, I haven&amp;rsquo;t really looked back, and it has quickly become one of my most favorite languages to program with. I feel like I find a new reason to love it more every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Its not a unit test - repost</title>
      <link>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/posts/its-not-a-unit-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 13:15:52 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/posts/its-not-a-unit-test/</guid>
      <description>This post is a reposting of one of my favorite blog posts about unit tests. It was originally posted by one of my colleagues at ThoughtWorks, but it came down when he decided to redesign his blog. I found it when I was starting out with unit testing and TDD and I think these rules really helped me to write some really good tests. Small, fast, and easy to maintain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fossflight</title>
      <link>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/projects/fossflight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 21:00:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.spargonaut.wtf/projects/fossflight/</guid>
      <description>FOSS Flight is the beginnings of an Eletronic Flight Bag (EFB).
I started FOSSFlight due to an interest in exploring Android development as well as a lot of frustrations with general aviation and the mobile apps that go with it.
I was frustrated with the quality of the EFBs and their ability to create, modify and use checklists, the most basic of tools used by pilots when flying.
I&amp;rsquo;ve also been frustrated with the cost of everything needed by the student pilot and the other non-commercial aviation enthusiasts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
